Guide to the Albert R. Mann papers, 1916-1931.
Mann, Albert R. papers, 1916-1931.
- State and Federal Related Materials, 1916-1931
  - Washington, D.C. (Miscellaneous), 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Washington, D.C. (Miscellaneous), 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Department of Farms and Markets, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Smith, Governor Alfred E., 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Smith, Governor Alfred E., 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Miller, Governor Nathan L., 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Zook, George F., Bureau of Education, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Secretary of State (Albany), 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Legislative, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Education Department (State), 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Education Department (State), 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Senate Relations Service, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Wallace, Henry C., 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Wallace, Henry C., 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Wallace, Henry C., 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    Allen, E. W.
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Architecture (State), 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Architecture (State), 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Attorney-General, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Board of Estimates and Control, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Board of Estimates and Control, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Civil Service, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Comptroller (State), 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Washington, D.C. (Miscellaneous), 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Washington, D.C. (Miscellaneous), 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Washington, D.C. (Miscellaneous), 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Washington, D.C. (Miscellaneous), 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Washington, D.C. (Miscellaneous), 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Department of Farms and Markets, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 54)
    Norgord, C. P.
    Foster, Frederic E.
  - Smith, Governor Alfred E., 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - Secretary of State (Albany), 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - Allen, E. W., 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - Wallace, Henry C., 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - Legislative, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - Education Department (State), 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 61)
  - Education Department (State), 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 62)
  - States Relations Service (General), 1923-1924 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Smith, C. B., 1923-1924 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Building Matters (1925-1926), 1925-1926 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Building Matters (1925-1926), 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Building Matters (1925-1926), 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - Architect - State, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Attorney - General, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Attorney - General, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - Board of Estimates and Control, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Comptroller - State, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - Washington, D.C. - Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - Washington, D.C. - Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - Smith, Governor Alfred E., 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - Secretary of State, Albany, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 71)
  - Department of Farms and Markets, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 72)
  - Allen, E. W., 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 73)
  - Wallace, Henry C., 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 74)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 75)
  - Legislative, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 76)
  - Educational Department, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 77)
  - Smith, C. B., 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 78)
  - States Relations Service - General, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 79)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Architect - State, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Attorney-General, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Board of Estimate and Control, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - Comptroller - State, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - Comptroller - State, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - Washington, D.C. - Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 54)
  - Smith, C. B., 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 55)
  - Farms and Markets, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 56)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - Jardine, W. M., 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 58)
  - Smith, Governor Alfred E., 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 59)
  - Secretary of State, Albany, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 60)
  - Legislative, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 61)
  - Education Department, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 62)
  - Architect - State, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Civil Service, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Board of Estimate and Control, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Board of Estimate and Control, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Comptroller - State, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Washington, D. C. - Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Washington, D. C. - Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Washington, D. C. - Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Washington, D. C. - Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Washington, D. C. - Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Washington, D. C. - Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Farms and Markets, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Jardine, W. M., 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Alfred E., 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of State - Albany, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Allen, E. W., 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Legislative, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Legislative, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Education Department, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Education Department, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Education Department, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 57)
    Hedrick, U. P.
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 67)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 68)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 69)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 70)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (also, 1926), 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 71)
  - Material re. Directorship at Geneva, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 72)
  - Material re. Directorship at Geneva, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 73)
  - Architect - State, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 74)
  - Board of Estimate and Control, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 75)
  - Comptroller - State, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 76)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 77)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 78)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 79)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 80)
  - Agriculture and Markets, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 81)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 82)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 83)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 84)
  - Allen, E. W., 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 85)
  - Smith, Alfred E., 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Jardine, W. M. - Secretary of Agriculture, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Education Department, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Graves, Frank P.
    Getman, A. K.
    Wilson, Lewis A.
  - Education Department, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Education Department, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Education Department, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Education Department, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of State, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - State Fair, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Department of Health, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Legislative, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Legislative, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - States Relations Service, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Architect - State, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Comptroller - State, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Zoology, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Agriculture and Markets, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Allen, E. W., 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Allen, E. W., 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Allen, E. W., 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Allen, E. W., 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Smith, Alfred E., 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Secretary of State, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Jardine, William M., 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Education Department, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Education Department, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Education Department, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Education Department, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Education Department, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - Education Department, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - Legislative, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - Legislative, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - U.S.D.A. Manuscripts, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - Report of Committee on Instruction in Agriculture, Home Economics, etc. - Land Grant College, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    Hucker, G. J.
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Comptroller - State, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Attorney-General, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Architect - State, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Agriculture and Markets, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Allen, E. W., 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Auchter, E. C. - U.S.D.A., 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Agriculture, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    Hyde, Arthur M.
  - Secretary of State, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Roosevelt, Governor Franklin D., 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Department of Public Works, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Legislative, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Federal Farm Board, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    New York State Farm Bureau
    Underwood, E. V.
    Foster, E. S.
  - Federal Farm Board, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Architect - State, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Architectural Advisory Board, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Comptroller - State, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Washington - Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Agriculture and Markets, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Roosevelt, Governor Franklin D., 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Evans, Walter H., 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Pyrke, Berne A., 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Legislative, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of State, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Agriculture, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Taxation and Finance, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Department of Health, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Federal Farm Board, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Conservation Commission, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Education Department, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Education Department, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Education Department, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Simpson, Alfred D., 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Horner, Harlan H., 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Horner, Harlan H., 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - Horner, Harlan H., 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 38)
- Subject Matter Files, 1906-1931
  - Disposition of Funds, Undated (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - Disposition of Funds, Undated (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - Disposition of Funds, Undated (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - Personal Memoranda, Undated (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - Personal Memoranda, Undated (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - Personal Memoranda, Undated (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - Personal Memoranda, Undated (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - Personal Memoranda, Undated (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - Galloway, Dr. (Beverly T.), Undated (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - The Fess Bill, of Home Economics Amendment, Undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - The Smith-Hughes Vocational Education Bill, Undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - 1929 Examination of College by Board of Estimate and Control, 1929 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Building Program Material, Undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Statements of Policy, Undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Teaching Load, Undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Program of Investigative Work and Report of Progress, Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, 1914-1915, 1914-1915 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, Hatch and Adams Projects, 1916-1917, 1916-1917 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Advisory Committee, Undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Material, Liberty Hyde Bailey, Undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Faculty, Undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Blauvelt Committee - Relation of University to State, Undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Reports and Correspondence: Cooperative Experiments with Field Crops, Problems in Agriculture, Make-Up Exams, Relation of Agriculture Teaching to Physics Department, Race Prejudice, Extension work, etc., Undated (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Reports and Correspondence: Cooperative Experiments with Field Crops, Problems in Agriculture, Make-Up Exams, Relation of Agriculture Teaching to Physics Department, Race Prejudice, Extension work, etc., Undated (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Reading Courses - letters form newspapermen, Undated (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Reading Courses - letters form newspapermen, Undated (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Liberty Hyde Bailey, Personal Documents, Undated (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Rural Social Conditions, Undated (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Rural Social Conditions, Undated (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Committee Report, New Athletic Field, 1906, 1906 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Statement re. Expenses, Budget Plans, Administrative Procedure and Business Methods of the New York State College of Agriculture at Cornell University, 1914, 1914 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Rural Service Building Committee, Undated (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Forestry Folder, Undated (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Forestry Folder, Undated (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Forestry Folder, Undated (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Forestry Folder, Undated (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Location of Buildings, College of Agriculture, Undated (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, Undated (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper Clippings: McCann of Butter, Feed, etc., Undated (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Farmingdale Situation, Undated (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Geneva Meger and Other Matters, Undated (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Syracuse University, Undated (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Syracuse University, Undated (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Newspaper Clippings: New York State College of Agriculture, Undated (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Legislative - State and National, Undated (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Purnell Bill, Undated (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Alpha Zeta, Undated (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Alpha Zeta, Undated (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Pack, Charles Lathrop, Undated (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Pack, Charles Lathrop, Undated (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Pack, Charles Lathrop, Undated (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Pack, Charles Lathrop, Undated (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - Tropical School of Agriculture, Puerto Rico, Undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Tropical School of Agriculture, Puerto Rico, Undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Tropical School of Agriculture, Puerto Rico, Undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Standing Committees, Undated (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Statistics of Graduate Students at Cornell University, 1909-1927; Work and Needs of the New York State College of Agriculture at Cornell University, 1919, 1909-1927 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Committee to Consider Agriculture in Relation to Proceedings of Constitutional Convention, Undated (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Employment of Extension Workers on 9-month Basis - Dr. True, Undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Status of Extension Workers as Faculty Members, Undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Thomas S. Whitbeck: Recollections of Ezra Cornell Farm Activities Prior to Founding of University, Undated (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Statistical Information of Leading Agricultural Colleges, Undated (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Regulations: Salary, Tuition, Vacation, 1916-1921, 1916-1921 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Material for Ferris Committee, 1921, 1921 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Material for Ferris Committee, 1921, 1921 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Hotel Course - Early Correspondence, 1921-1929, 1921-1929 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Hotel Course - Early Correspondence, 1921-1929, 1921-1929 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Hotel Course - Early Correspondence, 1921-1929, Undated (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Hotel Course - Early Correspondence, 1921-1929, Undated (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Hotel Course - Early Correspondence, 1921-1929, Undated (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Hotel Course - Early Correspondence, 1921-1929, Undated (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Hotel Course - Early Correspondence, 1921-1929, Undated (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Hotel Course - Early Correspondence, 1921-1929, Undated (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - General Education Board, 1927-1931, 1927-1931 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - General Education Board, 1927-1931, 1927-1931 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - General Education Board, 1927-1931, 1927-1931 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - International Education Board, 1924-1931, 1924-1931 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - International Education Board, 1924-1931, 1924-1931 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - International Education Board, 1924-1931, 1924-1931 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - International Education Board, 1924-1931, 1924-1931 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - International Education Board, 1924-1931, 1924-1931 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Institute on Family Relations, Undated (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Institute on Family Relations, Undated (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Institute on Family Relations, Undated (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Institute on Family Relations, Undated (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Institute on Family Relations, Undated (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial, Undated (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial, Undated (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Beta Lactose, Undated (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - National Research Council, Undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - National Research Council, Undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - National Research Council, Undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Survey Reports from Departments, Undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Survey Reports from Departments, Undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Land Utilization Program, Undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Land Utilization Program, Undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Herman Frasch Foundation for Chemical Research, Undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - American Country Life Association, Undated (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Land-Grant College Association, Undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Forestry, 1930, 1930 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Forestry, 1930, 1930 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Forestry, 1930, 1930 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - State School of forestry at Syracuse, memo of understanding and correspondence relative to establishment of, 1930-1931, Undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Data on Conference, 1917-1918, Undated (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Data on Conference, 1917-1918, Undated (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, Undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous, A-Z Materials, 1916-1931
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Jordan, W. J.
  - Attorney General (State), 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Comptroller (State), 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Department of Agriculture (State), 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Wilson, Charles S.
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Herbert Hoover note thanking Mann for program for Food Sunday
    Pearson, Ray A.
    Hoover, Herbert
    Spillman, W. J.
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Department of Interior (Albany), 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Jarvis, C. D.
    Meritt, E. B.
  - Education Department (State), 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Hawkins, Layton S.
    Finley, J. H.
  - State Agricultural Society, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - State Relations Service, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Clinton, L. A.
  - State Relations Service, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - State Relations Service, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - State Relations Service, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - State Relations Service, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - State Relations Service, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Whitman, Charles S. (Governor), 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Orr, William A.
  - B Miscellaneous, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bailey, Liberty Hyde, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 22)